Carlos Almanza

(915) 433 - 8030

itscarlosalmanza@gmail.com

606 Walden Cir., Boulder, Colorado 80305

Profile

I am a very motivated person with a passion for learning, throughout my career I have used that to deliver great customer experiences. Along with multi tasking and great focus my driven personality is a great fit for either team or individual work environments. Though my most recent experience was not in the direct field my position is very customer obsessed.

Experience

CHEF SUPERVISOR, THE WESTIN HOTEL DIA; DENVER, CO - 2018-PRESENT

- Oversee all aspects of the cold banquet kitchen
- Scheduling employees
- Ordering product and cost control
- Planning accordingly to ensure event success
- Meet with all other departments involved to understand customer expectations
- Translations to non-english speaking employees or customers, translating department meetings
- Being readily available to assist customers consuming our product

LEAD COOK, THE WESTIN HOTEL DIA; DENVER, CO - 2016-2018

- Climbed from student to lead cook in the first year
- Fast paced and very high customer volume
- Ensured customers enjoyed their dining experience by cooking top level food
- Maintaining all company standards and keeping company values in mind
- Craft monthly specials and assist co-workers in anything I was available to

LEAD COOK, RULI'S INTERNATIONAL KITCHEN; EL PASO, TX - 2014-2015

- Line cooking
- Worked all stations and covered areas staying clean and organized
- Managing my time and tasks according to business

CUSTOMER SERVICE AGENT FOR AT&T, ALORICA; EL PASO, TX - 2012-2014

- Taking inbound calls from AT&T customers
- Resolve billing issues
- Create tickets for technical issues and connect customers to appropriate department
- Navigate company systems to acquire information needed to resolve issues
- Notating customer accounts for all interactions

Education

Auguste Escoffier School of Culinary Arts, Boulder, Colorado - Culinary Certificate, 2016

University of Denver, Denver, Colorado - Full Stack Coding Bootcamp, completion 3/2021

Skills

- Bilingual in Spanish and English
- Problem solving
- Time management
- Multitasking
- Organization
- Adaptable
- Customer service
- Quick learner
- HTML,CSS, JS novice

References

Scott Snodell, Executive Chef at Westin Hotel DIA, (303) 961-8468

Oriana Alati, Chef Supervisor at Ritz-Carlton Denver, (702) 202-9131

Erika Liberato, Art Director at Popsockets, (915) 539-5441

Ruben Altamira, Account Manager at Popsockets, (720) 205-2893